

# HASAMUDDIN AFZALI

GRAPHIC DESIGNER & WEB DEVELOPER

## **EDUCATION**

## **COMPUTER ENGINEERING**

Karabük University 2022

#### **COMPUTER PROGRAMMING**

Karabük University 2019-2021

## CONTACT

#### **Address**

Bayır Mahalles Summer Cad. Apt.25, Karabük/TURKİYE 78100

#### **Phone**

+90 541 565 45 60

## **Email**

hasamuddin.afz@gmail.com

# LANGUAGE

Turkish, Fluent

Persian, Native

**English, Intermediate** 

## **ABOUT ME**

Hasamuddin Atfzlai is a talented young professional hailing from Karabuk, Turkey. Born in 2000, Hasamuddin has always been passionate about technology and computers. Currently 23 years old, he is pursuing a major in Computer Engineering at Karabuk University.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

2020-2021 INTERN

GENÇ BİLGİSAYAR

Trained users in proper use and care of computers to reduce and eliminate potentially damaging errors. Added new hardware, software, security patches and other updates to improve functionality of computer systems.

2021-2023 GRAPHIC

GRAPHIC DESIGNER BİRLİK AJANS

As a Graphic Designer successfully undertaken projects involving the design of flyers, logos, and restaurant menus for a diverse range of clients, showcasing his expertise and proficiency in graphic design.

## SKILL

Adobe photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Php

HTML-5/CSS-3